

## CONTACT

+32491632234

mathiaswouters.netlify.app

Oud-Turnhout, Belgium



LinkedIn



**Twitter** 

# MATHIAS WOUTERS

# **CLOUD & CYBER** SECURITY STUDENT

#### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Mathias Wouters, and I'm 21 years old. Currently, I'm studying Cloud and Cyber Security. I am social, friendly, stressresistant, responsible, and ambitious. In my free time, I like to read books and keep myself busy with new technologies.

#### **EDUCATION**

Thomas More, Geel | 2021 - now **Bachelor Cloud & Cyber Security** 

HT20, Turnhout | 2019 - 2021 **Electromechanics** 

Sint-Pietersinstituut, Turnhout | 2014 - 2019 **Mathematics & Sciences** 

#### **EXPERIENCES**

Job student | 2017 - 2023

#### Colruvt

- Help customers
- Fill shelves
- Working at the cash register

Job student | 2023 - now

#### **Get Driven**

80%

70%

- Professional customer interaction
- Providing chauffeur services
- Responsible handling of customers/vehicles

#### **HOBBIES**

Scout leader

Traveling

Reading books

### **SKILLS**

Linux Cloud (AWS - Azure) Kubernetes & Docker 75%

Python

Cisco Networking

Windows

Dutch - Mother tongue

English - C1

**LANGUAGES** 

French - B1

German - A1